-MY INVISILINE HAS
FINALLLY... (LAUGHTER)
-I HAVE TAKEN OUT MY INVISILINE
-I HAVE TAKEN OUT
MY INVISILINE, AND THIS IS THE
ALBUM
(LAUGHTER)
♪♪♪
♪ WHITE SHIRT ♪
♪ NOW RED MY BLOODY NOSE ♪
♪ SLEEPING ♪
♪ YOU'RE ON YOUR TIPPY TOES ♪
♪ CREEPING ♪
♪ AROUND LIKE NO ONE KNOWS ♪
♪ THINK YOU'RE SO CRIMINAL ♪
♪ BRUISES ♪
♪ ON BOTH MY KNEES FOR YOU ♪
♪ DON'T SAY ♪
♪ THANK YOU OR PLEASE I DO ♪
♪ WHAT I ♪
♪ WANT WHEN I'M WANTING TO ♪
♪ MY SOUL? SO CYNICAL ♪
♪ SO YOU'RE A TOUGH GUY ♪
♪ LIKE IT REALLY ROUGH GUY ♪
♪ JUST CAN'T GET
ENOUGH GUY ♪
♪ CHEST ALWAYS
SO PUFFED GUY ♪
♪ I'M THAT BAD TYPE ♪
♪ MAKE YOUR MAMA SAD TYPE ♪
♪ MAKE YOUR
GIRLFRIEND MAD TIGHT ♪
♪ MIGHT SEDUCE
YOUR DAD TYPE ♪
♪ I'M THE BAD GUY ♪
♪ DUH ♪
♪♪♪
♪ I'M THE BAD GUY ♪
♪ I LIKE ♪
♪ IT WHEN YOU TAKE CONTROL ♪
♪ EVEN ♪
♪ IF YOU KNOW
THAT YOU DON'T ♪
♪ OWN ME ♪
♪ I'LL LET YOU PLAY THE ROLE ♪
♪ I'LL BE ♪
♪ YOUR ANIMAL ♪
♪ MY MOMMY ♪
♪ LIKES TO SING ALONG ♪
♪ WITH ME ♪
♪ BUT SHE WON'T
SING THE SONG ♪
♪ IF SHE ♪
♪ READS ALL THE LYRICS ♪
♪ SHE'LL PITY ♪
♪ THE MEN I KNOW ♪
♪ SO YOU'RE A TOUGH GUY ♪
♪ LIKE IT REALLY ROUGH GUY ♪
♪ JUST CAN'T GET ENOUGH GUY ♪
♪ CHEST ALWAYS SO PUFFED GUY ♪
♪ I'M THAT BAD TYPE ♪
♪ MAKE YOUR MAMA SAD TYPE ♪
♪ MAKE YOUR
GIRLFRIEND MAD TIGHT ♪
♪ MIGHT SEDUCE
YOUR DAD TYPE ♪
♪ I'M THE BAD GUY ♪
♪ DUH ♪
♪♪♪
♪ I'M THE BAD GUY ♪
♪ DUH ♪
♪♪♪
♪ I'M ONLY GOOD
AT BEING BAD ♪
♪ BAD ♪
♪♪♪
♪ I LIKE WHEN
YOU GET MAD ♪
♪ I GUESS I'M
PRETTY GLAD ♪
♪ THAT YOU'RE ALONE ♪
♪ YOU SAID SHE'S
SCARED OF ME? I MEAN... ♪
♪ I DON'T SEE WHAT SHE SEES ♪
♪ BUT MAYBE IT'S CUZ ♪
♪ I'M WEARING YOUR COLOGNE ♪
♪♪♪
♪ I'M A BAD GUY ♪
♪ BAD GUY BAD GUY ♪
♪♪♪